(Penny:)Can you please come get him?
Uh, yeah, I'd be happy to, Penny.
[HOWARD IMITATES ALARM]
LEONARD: Oh, my God,
there's a breach in the radiation unit.
(Leonard:)The whole city is in jeopardy.
Oh, my God. Professor Guggenheim
is melting. Gotta go. Bye.
- I feel really guilty.
RAJESH: You did what you had to do.
HOWARD [IMITATES CHARLTON HESTON]:
Take your stinking paws off my popcorn...
(Howard:)...you damn dirty ape.
(Sheldon:)Thanks for bringing me home.
(Penny:)Oh, it's okay.
I didn't really need to work today.
(Penny:)It's not like I have rent
or car payments or anything.
(Sheldon:)Good, good.
(Penny:)Okay, well, you feel better.
(Sheldon:)Wait. Where are you going?
Um, home to write some bad checks.
(Sheldon:)You're going to leave me?
(Penny:)Sheldon, you are a grown man.
Haven't you ever been sick before?